Nirajkumar Singh

Address:

206/4, Chankyapuri, Ghatlodia, Ahmedabad

Pin Code: 380061

India.

E-mail Id: Nirajkumar.uk26@gmail.com

Nationality: Indian

M. No: +91 7600634764

Profile

I am a good team leader as well as a good team member and have participated in various team activities as a team leader. I have done many successful researches as well as prepared many financial reports. I am an adaptable, versatile and innovative graduate who has an ability to inspire other's; can easily work on Microsoft office, Payroll and Tally software. I am searching for an opportunity to get job to increase and develop my skills.

Current studies

Staffordshire University Jan 2014- June 2015

Master of Business AdministrationGradeRisk and Financial AnalysisFirst classInternational Supply Chain ManagementFirst classGlobal Strategic ManagementFirst class

Education and Qualification

International School of Management Studies, Pune, India
Edexcel BTEC Level 7 Extended Diploma in

2012 - 2013
Grade: Pass (2:1)

Strategic Management and Leadership

- Managing Financial Principles And Techniques
- Research Methods For Strategic Managers
- Project Development And Implementation For Strategic Managers
- Professional Development For Strategic Managers
- Strategic Human Resource Management
- Developing Strategic And Managerial Leadership Skills
- Strategic Quality And Systems Management

N.R. Institute of Business Administration, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India 2009 – 2012 Bachelor of Business Management

Management Accountancy
 Grade: First class (2:1)

• Advanced Human Resource Management

H.S.C Gujarat Board 2009 S.S.C Gujarat Board 2007 82%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Staff Indian Society (a society at Staffordshire) June 2014 to May2015

Appointed as a Finance manager to carry out all financial activities of society: including budget planning, budget control, fund raising, auditing, and book keeping.

Internship

Offer Beat (a local Search Engine) Pune, India

10th Oct 2012 to 24th July 2013

Approached by the Research and Development department of offer beat: to carry out a research on the scope for the new local search engine in the local market and to prepare a project to successfully launch a local search engine in Pune. It included market research, project management and meetings with customers and market experts.

EMPLOYABILITY SKILLS

- Analyzer: I am a very good analyzer and investigator in different situations as well as tasks given to
 me. I have an ability to evaluate things from different aspects. This makes me good decision maker
 also
- Time Management: I have always planned out all the things to be done in the whole day, week, and year and have been doing this for the past six years so that I can achieve my dream. Time Management has been grown over the years as I had a lot of project to be done in college and had to submit each project on time where I even had a time table for this.
- Negotiation: I have always been very particular about spending money on the things I need and how to negotiate on the things I want.
- Versatile: I am an adaptable graduate who can easily adjust with different role and utilise maximum resource available to achieve goal.

INTERESTS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- In my masters I have got academic excellence award, Total quality management award and best market research of the year.
- I have participated and won volleyball championship in 2007 at AakhilBhartiya Volleyball Championship in Gujarat.
- I have won the Table Tennis Championship in 2012 at International School of Management Studies, Pune. India.
- Travelling the world has always been my passion, Experiencing different cultures and their natural resources has always been another great interest.

REFEREES

Andrew Hirst BSc MBA PhD PGCE(HE) FHEA
Senior Lecturer Award Leader MBA & IPA STMC/GIST
Business School
Faculty of Business, Education and Law
Staffordshire University
Telephone Number +441782295861
e-mail a.p.hirst@staffs.ac.uk

Mrigakshi Sharma International School of Management Studies Pune- India. Professor of personality development Mobile number: +91 9881804411